all right artists you have seven hours
to freehand your tattoo and your time
starts now
all right brother let's do it I'm gonna
shave you and get your back prepped and
then I'm gonna lay with some stuff on
your back and see what happens today
we're testing composition and this is a
perfect way because free handing
something onto the body allows for
perfect placement it allows for flow it
allows it for the design to move with
the muscle or body part take your stairs
out to actually felt like this
yeah a lot easier if you're proficient
at what you do you can draw directly on
the skin use that as your guideline and
sail away
hello drawing these things bangerang I'm
all done she has a speed demon
growing up I didn't have a whole lot of
friends I was just like this weird kid
drawing was a way for me to escape that
reality and put myself in a new one you
got the okay let's start
[Music]
I'm getting nowhere on the back if I put
the flag there it's not really gonna
show great composition if there isn't a
reason for it where the flag would have
to come stop so weird it's not like
working if you do cap it's just gonna be
a better area to do it you're gonna get
what you want and still be able to you
know get an awesome piece rocket girl
now I have to redesign this entire thing
your drawing I just want a final design
to look at when I'm done we know why are
you gonna draw it on a piece of paper
again draw it on the calf that's your
paper five hours left guys five more
hours what do you think about just like
one line in like some of these feathers
like I'm liking that because it's great
yeah
Phoenix is everything that is flowy its
feathers it's loose and pawn is used to
structured fold solid shapes I think
that's a perfect solution flowy is not
what he does they gave me this think
they were tripping me up and like I
don't know what did he try my man
that's I'm saying and it's just so weird
good for you Jake Duke doesn't do
anything I haven't seen you dress so
glad I could do the thing I do every
single day back at home do I do a lot of
wolves and wolves they're very similar
to a fox so I have a lot of confidence
going into this see all this I don't
know if that's like their skins like
that or that hi it's scar tissue that
you have in your skin that you wouldn't
notice until it gets irritated and as
you tattoo don't pop up more packing is
like almost impossible just scratch it
all in there quickly and then go work on
something else and come back to it and
that's getting done is open and we'll
take it right no that makes sense yeah
the hardest part about tattooing is the
canvases skin is constantly changing
kind of worried about not finishing
you kind of throw blacks in we're
towards the end yeah this side I want to
do like nice solid blacks black and gray
is pretty boring most of the time if I
have the option to do color versus black
and gray we is doing color since your
light source is coming from the right
just a couple of real strong blacks on
the left making sure your whole right
side is later I don't feel like I have
to prove anything to anyone I just want
to do cool tattoos I'm gonna sit and
draw my own background stuff to see if
there's anything I can come up with that
but I feel confident in I'm a total
narcissist
I just want to impress myself three
hours left three more hours left
I am learning so much they called me
like the queen of the bottom because I
got don't know a lot of style said I
don't hold me do black and gray realism
yeah ash shut up keep that I know I'm
not worse this is why I like I was like
when you're talking you late Ted shut it
I'm always like I'll need your stories
need to get your nails finished I'm
excited to do this koi fish it's out of
my comfort zone it's on my wheelhouse
why not wing it I lost my mom because I
know it's hard she had small cell lung
cancer and I was working as an
apprentice and I quit everything and I
oh I took care of it
just because my life is ending doesn't
mean yours is gonna night exactly I
think my won't be proud I am persevered
through a lot are you getting a nice
tattoo understand so proud of her okay
beautiful what's half of the show I just
got away I would use like your darkest
like red orange that you used do texture
yeah it's not that bad
okay I feel like the pressure that's on
me now is higher my one tattoo of the
day last week that was rad and I'm just
trying to live up to the standard that
I've set for myself the real trick is
knowing when to like stop
[Music]
five four three two one that's it scenes
down time is up no more ink
yo we are done dude this absolutely
awesome - I can't believe in yourself
I'm going to throw up immediately after
this collapse don't you get it done
I don't further stop it doesn't look
unfinished my poster miles to actually
try to finish that you want your big kid
there's what the really think about it
[Music]